{
  "name": "2-Flips UF",
  "buffers": "UF",
  "pool": [
    {
      "id": 856,
      "prompt": "[UF] [UL]",
      "solution": "L F' L' U M' U2 M U S' L F L' S"
    },
    {
      "id": 864,
      "prompt": "[UF] [DL]",
      "solution": "L F' L' S U' M' U2 M U' L F L' S'"
    },
    {
      "id": 863,
      "prompt": "[UF] [DB]",
      "solution": "U2 M U' S R' F' R S' R' F R U' M'"
    },
    {
      "id": 861,
      "prompt": "[UF] [DF]",
      "solution": "U L F L' S' L F' L' S U' M' U2 M U2"
    },
    {
      "id": 860,
      "prompt": "[UF] [BL]",
      "solution": "E' R' U' R E R2 E2 R U R' E2 R2"
    },
    {
      "id": 862,
      "prompt": "[UF] [DR]",
      "solution": "R' F R S' U M' U2 M U R' F' R S"
    },
    {
      "id": 858,
      "prompt": "[UF] [FR]",
      "solution": "R U' R' E' R2 E2 R' U R E2 R2 E"
    },
    {
      "id": 859,
      "prompt": "[UF] [BR]",
      "solution": "R S' R' F R U' M' U2 M U' S R' F'"
    },
    {
      "id": 854,
      "prompt": "[UF] [UB]",
      "solution": "U' S R' F' R S' R' F R U' M' U2 M"
    },
    {
      "id": 857,
      "prompt": "[UF] [FL]",
      "solution": "R' E R U' R' E' R2 E2 R' U R E2 R'"
    }
  ]
}
